free-ringtones.cc 2012-01-01

# Free iPhone Ringtones

(Last Updated 3/24/2011)

Welcome to free-ringtones.cc  
BY USING OR ACCESSING THE SITE OR ANY OF THE SERVICES, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF ANYTHING HERE OFFENDS YOU OR YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY IT, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITE OR ANY OF ITS SERVICES.  
This Privacy Policy should be read together and in conjunction with our binding Terms of Use ("Terms").   
Any term defined in the Terms shall have the same meaning under this Policy.

First and foremost you should know that anything and everything you post, upload, send to anyone or publish within the Site and its services is never private, can and will be accessible for others for a long period of time and also may be posted by the Site, anywhere on the Site. Therefore, please DO NOT POST ANYTHING YOU WISH TO REMAIN CONFIDENTIAL OR IN BREACH OF ANYONE'S RIGHT. 

#### What We Collect, and How:

When you access the Service, we may (but under no obligation to) collect non-personally identifiable information such as, but not limited to, user data, browser type, log information and IP address using "cookies" or other methods.   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer holding information about you. This information may be gathered for all users and may be used by us to improve the Site, to offer a better experience using the Site, to offer more useful advertising or promotional material, etc.   
You may configure your web-browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, per browser's definitions. However, in order to use some of the services you might have to enable accepting cookies from us. 

When you post any content to the Site, we also may collect the following information: Your chosen nickname of that session, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the time and date of such posting and the content of such post. This information, alongside any other non-identifiable information, is being stored by us and may be used subject to this Policy.  
Apart from the mentioned above and the material you load on to the Site, the Site does not collect any details of any kind of its users

Please note that such information or any part thereof may be available to other persons using the Site. You are specifically aware that we may allow access to some or all past content, information and posts as we may decide at any relevant time. Showing or hiding such information, content and posts may not allow you or anyone else any claim against us, for any cause whatsoever.  
We may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contacts with us by email or by any other way.

#### Use of Information, Sharing and Disclosure:

Please take notice that whenever you voluntarily post any content using the Site, that content can be accessed by anyone using the Internet and we cannot be and are not responsible to any result of such exposure.   
Any hosting of content on the Site is NEVER private, and we may allow free access to the content at our discretion, including adding any content to the Site's index available to the users for further download and review.  
We may use any of your non-identifying or personal information to: 

  * better personalize the Site to your and to other user's taste;
  * provide the Service you request;
  * offer better and more interesting services;
  * manage the Site and resolve any relevant disputes, if applicable; 
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms and this Policy;
  * send you targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers, both from the Site or third parties; 
  * exchange or transfer information to third parties who wish to offer you commercial and other benefits.

We may use by ourselves or share information and content with third parties for the purpose of sending you promotional and advertising products and services in order to allow you a better and more targeted experience.  
We may further disclose the information and content stored by us, including any personally identifiable information about you, in the following instances:

  * We believe, in our sole discretion, that the law requires us or we have to respond to the legal authority of any relevant jurisdiction.
  * We have been requested to do so by an authorized authority, by court order or by similar procedure;
  * We believe, in our sole discretion, that your actions while you were using the Site violate our Terms, any law, any agreement or any third party's rights;
  * We believe, in our sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary to prevent or minimize physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or may be interfering with the our rights or property, with those of other users or any third party. 

Any information collected by us may be stored and processed in Israel or in any other country in which we or our affiliates, subsidiaries or agents may maintain facilities, and by using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.   
We may sell or otherwise transfer your information to third parties to allow you a better and more targeted exposure to their products and services.  
We may transfer any and all content, personal information and other information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale, merger, acquisition or any other transaction with the Site or substantially all of its assets.   
We may also make any use of the content you post on the Service, as detailed in our Terms.  
By using the Site or Services, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in Israel. 

#### Third Party Advertising on the Service

Advertisements that appear on the Service might be delivered to users by third party advertisers or partners. Such third parties may automatically receive your IP address and some other details when this happens. These third party advertisers may also use cookies, or other tracking technologies to offer you better services. In this way, they may gather certain information regarding the Internet use from your computer in order to send them more relevant and targeted advertising (such as what advertisements were viewed or clicked on). We do not have access to or control of those cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. This Policy does not cover those cookies or advertisers. **__**

#### Changing or Removing Information

You may report any inaccuracies in personal information or other information which you wish to edit by e-mailing us at [webmaster@free-ringtones.cc](mailto:webmaster@free-ringtones.cc) . We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies.

#### Links

The site may contain links to other websites. Of course the Site will not responsible for the privacy practices of those other web sites. Please be cautious when you use other websites and follow their privacy statement as well. 

#### Consent:

By using the Service, you consent to the collection and use of the above-described information us or anyone on our behalf.

#### Notification of Changes:

We reserve the right to update this Policy in the same manner as updating our Terms.   
It is your responsibility to review this Policy for changes and make sure you agree to each current policy. If you do not agree, please make no use of the Service as such use constitutes agreement to the updated Policy as well.. 

#### Contacting Us:

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you are invited to contact us by using the "Contact Us" links or by emailing us to 

_[webmaster@free-ringtones.cc](mailto:webmaster@free-ringtones.cc)_
